bigtex.com 2019-07-16

# State Fair of Texas Privacy Policy | State Fair of Texas

The State Fair of Texas (“we” or “us”) maintains an e-mail list of customers (age 18 or older) who have expressed an interest in events sponsored or offered by the State Fair of Texas and have provided to us certain personal information, either in writing or online. Your submission of your name and email address and any other personal information, as applicable, indicates your acceptance of this Privacy Policy and your acknowledgment that you are at least 18 years of age or older.

**Our Commitment to Privacy**  
Your privacy is important to the State Fair of Texas. For this reason, we provide you with this notice explaining how we will use the information that you provide.

**The Information We Collect**  
This policy applies only to the information that you provide to the State Fair of Texas and may include any of the following (“Contact Information”):

Name  
E-mail address  
Telephone number  
Physical address

**How We Use your Contact Information**  
The State Fair of Texas will not sell or rent your personally identifiable Contact Information to anyone. However, the State Fair of Texas may share such information with other companies or people when:

We have your consent to share the information;  
We need to share your information to provide the products, information, or services you have requested; or We have a third-parties assist us in providing promotional materials and information about upcoming events sponsored or produced by the State Fair of Texas.

By providing your Contact Information to us, you consent to our right to use such information and authorize us to share this information with companies who work on behalf of the State Fair of Texas to provide a product, information or service to you.

Also to facilitate your use of our website at www.bigtex.com (“Website”), we may store certain types of information that we receive whenever an Internet user visits our Website. A “cookie” is a small alphanumeric identifier file that can be transferred to your computer’s hard drive through your web browser that would enable our systems to recognize your browser. We may use cookies on some pages of our Website, for example, to obtain information about your actions and the web pages you visited. The cookie, by itself, doesn’t tell us (or anyone else) who you are, your email address, or anything else personal.

**Links to Other Websites**  
On our Website, we may have external links to other websites. We are not responsible for the content on these websites or the privacy policies and practices of the operators of these websites. Therefore, we recommend that you review the terms of use and privacy policy for each third-party website.

**Party Collecting the Information**  
This Privacy Policy only addresses the use and dissemination of information that we collect from you. To the extent that you disclose any information to other parties, whether through, for example, online auctions, chat rooms, personal ads, or the like, through third party services or promotions offered on or through the Site or through other Web sites throughout the Internet, different policies may apply and the Fair shall not be responsible for the use or dissemination of such information.

Third parties may use cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies to collect or receive information from this website and use that information to provide measurement services and target Facebook, Twitter and Display ads. If you’d like to opt-out from having our partners collect your Non-Personally Identifiable Information on behalf of State Fair of Texas, please click <http://ib.adnxs.com/optout>. When you opt out, we will place an opt-out cookie on your computer. The opt-out cookie tells us not to collect your Non-PII to help us tailor our online advertisement campaigns. Please note that if you delete, block or otherwise restrict cookies, or if you use a different computer or Internet browser, you may need to renew your opt-out choice.

Users may opt-out of the collection and use of information for Facebook ad targeting visiting [facebook.com/ads/website_custom_audiences/](http://facebook.com/ads/website_custom_audiences/).

Users may opt-out of the collection and use of information for Twitter ad targeting by visiting <https://support.twitter.com/articles/20170405>.

**Our Commitment to Children’s Privacy**  
Our Website is not intended to be directed at children, and we have no intention of collecting any personal information from individuals under the age of thirteen (13). We require all users who submit Contact Information to us in writing or via our Website to be at least eighteen (18) years of age or older.

**Our Commitment to Data Security**  
The State Fair of Texas is committed to preventing the unauthorized access your personally identifiable information and will take commercially reasonable measures to prevent the unauthorized access and use of such information.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
The State Fair of Texas may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your Contact Information we will post a prominent announcement on our website at www.bigtex.com. Therefore, we recommend that from time to time, you review our website to check for any changes or modifications.

**How to Contact Us**  
You may opt out of receiving emails from us by sending such request to us at [info@bigtex.com](mailto:info@bigtex.com) or by selecting the “opt out” option on any email sent to you.

State Fair of Texas® and Summer Adventures in Fair Park® are the marks of the State Fair of Texas and may not be used or reproduced without our written permission.
